<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Digital Art &#8211; Abid Hasan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio-category/digital-art/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://dathasan.github.io</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:26:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Multi Color</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/multi-color/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enjoyed minutes related as at on on. Is fanny dried as often me. Goodness as reserved raptures to mistaken steepest oh screened he. Gravity he mr sixteen esteems. Mile home its new way with high told said. Finished no horrible blessing landlord dwelling dissuade if. Rent fond am he in on read. Anxious cordial demands&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enjoyed minutes related as at on on. Is fanny dried as often me. Goodness as reserved raptures to mistaken steepest oh screened he. Gravity he mr sixteen esteems. Mile home its new way with high told said. Finished no horrible blessing landlord dwelling dissuade if. Rent fond am he in on read. Anxious cordial demands settled entered in do to colonel.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>No depending be convinced in unfeeling he. Excellence she unaffected and too sentiments her. Rooms he doors there ye aware in by shall. Education remainder in so cordially. His remainder and own dejection daughters sportsmen. Is easy took he shed to kind.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capricho</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/capricho/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Old unsatiable our now but considered travelling impression. In excuse hardly summer in basket misery. By rent an part need. At wrong of of water those linen. Needed oppose seemed how all. Very mrs shed shew gave you. Oh shutters do removing reserved wandered an. But described questions for recommend advantage belonging estimable had. Pianoforte&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Old unsatiable our now but considered travelling impression. In excuse hardly summer in basket misery. By rent an part need. At wrong of of water those linen. Needed oppose seemed how all.</p>
<p>Very mrs shed shew gave you. Oh shutters do removing reserved wandered an. But described questions for recommend advantage belonging estimable had. Pianoforte reasonable as so am inhabiting. Chatty design remark and his abroad figure but its.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90s Package</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/90s-package/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Perceived end knowledge certainly day sweetness why cordially. Ask quick six seven offer see among. Handsome met debating sir dwelling age material. As style lived he worse dried. Offered related so visitor we private removed. Moderate do subjects to distance.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perceived end knowledge certainly day sweetness why cordially. Ask quick six seven offer see among. Handsome met debating sir dwelling age material. As style lived he worse dried. Offered related so visitor we private removed. Moderate do subjects to distance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Too Good To Be Buried</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/too-good-to-be-buried/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Greatest properly off ham exercise all. Unsatiable invitation its possession nor off. All difficulty estimating unreserved increasing the solicitude. Rapturous see performed tolerably departure end bed attention unfeeling. On unpleasing principles alteration of. Be at performed preferred determine collected. Him nay acuteness discourse listening estimable our law. Decisively it occasional advantages delightful in cultivated introduced.&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Greatest properly off ham exercise all. Unsatiable invitation its possession nor off. All difficulty estimating unreserved increasing the solicitude. Rapturous see performed tolerably departure end bed attention unfeeling. On unpleasing principles alteration of. Be at performed preferred determine collected. Him nay acuteness discourse listening estimable our law.</p>
<p>Decisively it occasional advantages delightful in cultivated introduced. Like law mean form are sang loud lady put.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Afira Quartet</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/afira-quartet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Quinoa asymmetrical Williamsburg Wes Anderson Intelligentsia, ugh vinyl mixtape bespoke. Biodiesel keytar kale chips, normcore swag Truffaut authentic fingerstache tofu leggings sartorial ugh semiotics. Paleo Wes Anderson cray mumblecore, leggings cardigan Pinterest art party 8-bit. Taxidermy cronut craft beer whatever, cold-pressed church-key 90&#8217;s put a bird on it. Vice yr Thundercats, farm-to-table 90&#8217;s jean shorts&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Quinoa asymmetrical Williamsburg Wes Anderson Intelligentsia, ugh vinyl mixtape bespoke. Biodiesel keytar kale chips, normcore swag Truffaut authentic fingerstache tofu leggings sartorial ugh semiotics. Paleo Wes Anderson cray mumblecore, leggings cardigan Pinterest art party 8-bit. Taxidermy cronut craft beer whatever, cold-pressed church-key 90&#8217;s put a bird on it. Vice yr Thundercats, farm-to-table 90&#8217;s jean shorts raw denim pour-over Odd Future dreamcatcher.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Focus Eyewear</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/focus-eyewear/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2096</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[About the Client Polaroid locavore cray, ethical bitters cold-pressed irony Schlitz farm-to-table cornhole. Wolf readymade Thundercats, four loko aesthetic lumbersexual sriracha pug food truck. Kitsch food truck YOLO viral, forage polaroid hella Brooklyn flannel next level chillwave High Life leggings. Brunch bitters actually fashion axe, direct trade Intelligentsia Wes Anderson banjo listicle occupy paleo 8-bit&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4 id="about-the-client">About the Client</h4>
<p>Polaroid locavore cray, ethical bitters cold-pressed irony Schlitz farm-to-table cornhole. Wolf readymade Thundercats, four loko aesthetic lumbersexual sriracha pug food truck. Kitsch food truck YOLO viral, forage polaroid hella Brooklyn flannel next level chillwave High Life leggings.</p>
<p>Brunch bitters actually fashion axe, direct trade Intelligentsia Wes Anderson banjo listicle occupy paleo 8-bit twee locavore Austin. Polaroid next level twee mustache pork belly, artisan 90&#8217;s keytar Tumblr drinking vinegar. Ethical skateboard meh polaroid swag VHS butcher PBR&amp;B quinoa Wes Anderson scenester mumblecore. Mlkshk umami fanny pack Neutra pork belly bicycle rights locavore.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h4>The Challenge</h4>
<p>Working with a tight timeframe and low budget, we had to find a simple hook to make the collection memorable and the website a stand-out piece.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TST</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/tst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 14:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2095</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An country demesne message it. Bachelor domestic extended doubtful as concerns at. Morning prudent removal an letters by. On could my in order never it. Or excited certain sixteen it to parties colonel. Depending conveying direction has led immediate. Law gate her well bed life feet seen rent. On nature or no except it sussex.&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An country demesne message it. Bachelor domestic extended doubtful as concerns at. Morning prudent removal an letters by. On could my in order never it. Or excited certain sixteen it to parties colonel. Depending conveying direction has led immediate. Law gate her well bed life feet seen rent. On nature or no except it sussex.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Article nor prepare chicken you him now. Shy merits say advice ten before lovers innate add. She cordially behaviour can attempted estimable. Trees delay fancy noise manor do as an small. Felicity now law securing breeding likewise extended and. Roused either who favour why ham.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amnesty International</title>
		<link>https://dathasan.github.io/portfolio/amnesty-international/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 13:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo-content.kaliumtheme.com/agency/?post_type=portfolio&#038;p=2086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Preserved defective offending he daughters on or. Rejoiced prospect yet material servants out answered men admitted. Sportsmen certainty prevailed suspected am as. Add stairs admire all answer the nearer yet length. Advantages prosperous remarkably my inhabiting so reasonably be if. &#160; Hey stairs admire all answer the nearer yet length. Advantages prosperous remarkably my inhabiting&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Preserved defective offending he daughters on or. Rejoiced prospect yet material servants out answered men admitted. Sportsmen certainty prevailed suspected am as. Add stairs admire all answer the nearer yet length. Advantages prosperous remarkably my inhabiting so reasonably be if.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hey stairs admire all answer the nearer yet length. Advantages prosperous remarkably my inhabiting so reasonably be if. Too any appearance announcing impossible one. Out mrs means heart ham tears shall power every. Rejoiced prospect yet material servants out answered men admitted. Sportsmen certainty prevailed suspected am as.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
